question_data = [{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The music group Daft Punk got their name from a negative review they recieved.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The song &quot;Megalovania&quot; by Toby Fox made its third appearence in the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Film","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The movie &quot;The Nightmare before Christmas&quot; was all done with physical objects.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The planet Mars has two moons orbiting it.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science: Computers","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"All program codes have to be compiled into an executable file in order to be run. This file can then be executed on any machine.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"&quot;Kamea,&quot; the Gilbertese Islander word for dog, is derived from the English phrase &quot;Come here!&quot;","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The country song  &ldquo;A Boy Named Sue&rdquo; was written by Shel Silverstein.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Politics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In 2016, the United Kingdom voted to stay in the EU.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"There are 6 legendary cards in &quot;Clash Royale&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The animated film &quot;Spirited Away&quot; won the Academy Award for Best Animated Feature at the 75th Academy Awards in 2003.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science: Mathematics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The binary number &quot;101001101&quot; is equivalent to the Decimal number &quot;334&quot;","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The anime &quot;Lucky Star&quot; follows the story of one girl who is unaware she is God.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Salt is 100% composed of Sodium.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The average woman is 5 inches \/ 13 centimeters shorter than the average man.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Scientists accidentally killed the once known world&#039;s oldest living creature, a mollusc, known to be aged as 507 years old.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Deadpool&#039;s identity is Slade Wilson.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"No Game No Life first aired in 2014.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The 2005 video game &quot;Call of Duty 2: Big Red One&quot; is not available on PC.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Film","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Samuel L. Jackson had the words, &#039;Bad Motherf*cker&#039; in-scripted on his lightsaber during the filming of Star Wars.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Film","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Alfred Hitchcock&#039;s film &#039;Psycho&#039; it is said he used chocolate syrup to simulate the blood in the famous shower scene from ","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Gosho Aoyama Made This Series: (Detective Conan \/ Case Closed!)","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"You could walk from Norway to North Korea while only passing through Russia.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Pok&eacute;mon, Ash&#039;s Pikachu refuses to go into a pokeball.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"History","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"United States President Ronald Reagan was the first president to appoint a woman to the Supreme Court. ","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The Lego Group was founded in 1932.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Film","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"&quot;Cube&quot;, &quot;Cube 2: Hypercube&quot; and &quot;Cube Zero&quot; were directed by the same person.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"An exothermic reaction is a chemical reaction that releases energy by radiating electricity.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"An Astronomical Unit is the distance between Earth and the Moon.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In RuneScape, one must complete the &quot;Dragon Slayer&quot; quest before equipping Rune Platelegs.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Politics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Donald Trump won the popular vote in the 2016 United States presidential election.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Television","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Bob Ross was a US Air Force pilot.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"&quot;Santa Claus&quot; is a variety of melon.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In &quot;Call Of Duty: World At War&quot;, the first appearance of the &quot;PPSH-41&quot; in &quot;Zombies&quot; was in the map &quot;Der Riese&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In &quot;To Love-Ru: Darkness&quot;, Yami reveals her real name is Eve.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Several characters in &quot;Super Mario 64&quot; blink their eyes, including Mario himself.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Celiac Disease is a disease that effects the heart, causing those effected to be unable to eat meat.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Television","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In &quot;Star Trek: The Next Generation&quot;, Data is the only android in existence.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Hidden in the files for &quot;Mario Kart Arcade GP&quot; is a picture of the Beslan school hostage crisis.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The song Scatman&#039;s World was released after Scatman (Ski-Ba-Bop-Ba-Dop-Bop).","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"&quot;Sonic the Hedgehog 2&quot; originally was going to have a time travel system.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Books","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"&quot;Green Eggs and Ham&quot; consists of only 50 different words.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In career mode of &quot;Need for Speed: Underground 2&quot;, the first car the player can drive is the BMW M3 GTR.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"You can tell the age of a ladybird by counting the spots on his back.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"In &quot;Minecraft&quot;, gold tools are faster than diamond tools.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The internet browser Firefox is named after the Red Panda.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science: Computers","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"A Boolean value of &quot;0&quot; represents which of these words?","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"History","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The man that shot Alexander Hamilton was named Aaron Burr.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"&quot;Neutral Milk Hotel&quot; is a real band.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Shang Tsung is a playable character in Mortal Kombat XL.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science: Computers","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The Python programming language gets its name from the British comedy group &quot;Monty Python.&quot;","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Nintendo started out as a playing card manufacturer.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The name of the main character of the video game &quot;The Legend of Zelda&quot;, is Zelda.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The Indie Game Development Studio Cing, developers of Hotel Dusk and Last Window, went bankrupt on March 1st, 2010.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The Mann Co. Store from Team Fortress 2 has the slogan &quot;We hire mercenaries and get in fights&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"Unturned originally started as a Roblox game.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Faust is a playable character in &quot;Guilty Gear Xrd Revelator&quot;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The Ace Attorney trilogy was suppose to end with &quot;Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney &minus; Trials and Tribulations&quot; as its final game.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In &quot;Overwatch,&quot; an allied McCree will say &quot;Step right up&quot; upon using his ultimate ability Deadeye.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"In &quot;Portal 2&quot;, Cave Johnson started out Aperture Science as a shower curtain company.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In Half-Life 2, if you play the zombies&#039; speech in reverse, they actually speak coherent English.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Minecraft can be played with a virtual reality headset.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the game Dead by Daylight, the killer Michael Myers is refered to as &quot;The Shape&quot;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Pok&eacute;mon, Bulbasaur is the only starter pokemon that is a Grass\/Poison type.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Mortal Kombat was almost based on Jean-Claude Van Damme movie.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In RuneScape, one must complete the &quot;Dragon Slayer&quot; quest before equipping Rune Platelegs.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The ADAM collecters in the Bioshock series are known as Little Sisters.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"&quot;Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater&quot; was released in 2004.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The ghosts in &quot;Pac-Man&quot; and &quot;Ms. Pac-Man&quot; have completely different behavior.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In &quot;League of Legends&quot;, there exists four different types of Dragon.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The game &quot;Pocket Morty&quot; has a Morty called &quot;Pocket Mortys Morty&quot;?","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Activision created Battlefield 1.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Hidden in the files for &quot;Mario Kart Arcade GP&quot; is a picture of the Beslan school hostage crisis.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In career mode of &quot;Need for Speed: Underground 2&quot;, the first car the player can drive is the BMW M3 GTR.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"During pre-production of &quot;Super Mario Bros.&quot;, Mario originally was meant to shoot bullets.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"In &quot;Minecraft&quot;, gold tools are faster than diamond tools.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In the game &quot;Until Dawn&quot; Emily is the only playable character who can be killed by another playable character directly.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Codemasters is the developer of the Gran Turismo series.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The game &quot;Jetpack Joyride&quot; was created by &quot;Redbrick Studios&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the Monster Hunter Series, it is possible to capture Elder Dragons.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"&quot;Resident Evil 7&quot; is the first first-person Resident Evil game.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}]
